<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FragmentAndFragmentFactory</string>
    <string name="bts_description">BTS (Korean: 방탄소년단; RR: Bangtan Sonyeondan), also known as the Bangtan Boys, is a seven-member South Korean boy band that began formation in 2010 and debuted in 2013 under Big Hit Entertainment.Originally a hip hop group, their musical style has evolved to include a wide range of genres. Their lyrics, often focused on personal and social commentary, touch on the themes of mental health, troubles of school-age youth and coming-of-age, loss, the journey towards loving oneself, and individualism. Their work features references to literature and psychological concepts and includes an alternative universe storyline. The group has released several albums and performed on several world tours.

Having sold over 20 million albums on the Gaon Music Chart, BTS is the best-selling artist in South Korean history and holds the best-selling album in South Korea with Map of the Soul: 7. They are the first and only Asian and non-English speaking act to be named the IFPI Global Recording Artist of the Year (2020) and to chart on Billboards Top Touring Artists of the 2010s

Throughout their career, BTS received numerous accolades for their work, including 6 American Music Awards, 9 Billboard Music Awards and 24 Golden Disk Awards, and nominations for a Grammy Award and a Brit Award. Following the establishment of their Love Myself anti-violence campaign in partnership with UNICEF, BTS addressed the United Nations 73rd and 75th General Assemblies and became the youngest ever recipients of the Order of Cultural Merit from the President of South Korea due to their contributions in spreading Korean culture and language.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name ="V">Kim Tae-hyung (Korean: 김태형; born December 30, 1995),also known by his stage name V, is a South Korean singer, songwriter, and actor. He is a vocalist of the South Korean boy group BTS.</string>
    <string name ="Jungkook">Jeon Jung-kook (Korean: 전정국; born September 1, 1997), better known mononymously as Jungkook, is a South Korean singer and songwriter. He is the youngest member of and vocalist in the South Korean boy band BTS.</string>
    <string name ="rm">Kim Nam-joon (Korean: 김남준; born September 12, 1994),[1] better known by his stage name RM (formerly Rap Monster), is a South Korean rapper, songwriter and record producer. He is the leader of the South Korean boy group BTS. In 2015, he released his first solo mixtape, RM. In October 2018, his second mixtape, Mono, was the highest-charting album by a Korean soloist on the Billboard 200 chart, having peaked at 26. He has recorded with artists such as Wale, Younha, Warren G, Gaeko, Krizz Kaliko, MFBTY, Fall Out Boy, Primary, and Lil Nas X.</string>
    <string name ="jhope">Jung Ho-seok (Korean: 정호석; born February 18, 1994), better known by his stage name J-Hope (stylized as j-hope), is a South Korean rapper, songwriter, dancer, and record producer. In 2013, J-Hope made his debut as a member of South Korean boy band BTS, managed under Big Hit Music.
J-Hope released his first solo mixtape, Hope World, worldwide on March 1, 2018. The album was met with a positive reception. His debut at number 63 (and subsequent peak at number 38) made him the highest-charting solo Korean artist on the Billboard 200 at the time of the mixtapes release. On September 27, 2019, he released his song ”Chicken Noodle Soup” featuring Becky G. On October 12, 2019, the solo single debuted at No. 81 on US Billboard Hot 100, which made him the first member of BTS with a Hot 100 hit under his own name.</string>
    <string name="jimin">Park Ji-min (Korean: 박지민; born October 13, 1995), better known mononymously as Jimin, is a South Korean singer, songwriter, and dancer. In 2013, he debuted as a member of the South Korean boy band BTS, under the record label Big Hit Entertainment.</string>
    <string name="jin">Kim Seok-jin (Korean: 김석진; born December 4, 1992), also known by his stage name Jin, is a South Korean singer, songwriter, and member of the South Korean boy band BTS since June 2013. Kim has co-written and released three solo tracks with BTS: "Awake" (2016), "Epiphany" (2018), and "Moon" (2020), all of which have charted on South Koreas Gaon Digital Chart. In 2019, Kim released his first independent song, the digital track "Tonight". He also appeared on the 2016 Hwarang: The Poet Warrior Youth soundtrack alongside BTS member V. Kim has received critical praise for his falsetto and emotional range as a singer.
Apart from singing, Kim has also appeared as a host on multiple South Korean music programs from 2016 to 2018. In 2018, he was awarded the fifth-class Hwagwan Order of Cultural Merit by the President of South Korea along with the other members of BTS, for his contributions to Korean culture.</string>
    <string name="suga">Min Yoon-gi (Korean: 민윤기; born March 9, 1993), better known by his stage names Suga (stylized as SUGA) and Agust D,[A] is a South Korean rapper, songwriter and record producer. Managed by Big Hit Music, he debuted as a member of the South Korean pop idol group BTS in 2013. In 2016, he released his first solo mixtape, Agust D. In 2018, he re-released the mixtape for digital purchase and streaming. The reissue reached number three on Billboards World Albums Chart. In 2020, he released his second solo mixtape, D-2. Commercially, the mixtape peaked at number 11 on the US Billboard 200, number seven on the UK Albums Chart, and number two on Australias ARIA Album Chart. The Korea Music Copyright Association attributes over 100 songs to Suga as a songwriter and producer, including Surans "Wine" which peaked at number two on the Gaon Music Chart and won best Soul/R and B track of the year at the 2017 Melon Music Awards.</string>
</resources>